[
  {
    "question": "Amanda's favorite animals are cats",
    "answer": true
  },

  {
    "question": "Animals favorite cats are Amanda",
    "answer": false
  },

  {
    "question": "What the function do",
    "answer": false
  },

  {
    "question": "Did you click the last button",
    "answer": true
  },

  {
    "question": "Cats don't taste sweetness",
    "answer": true
  },

  {
    "question": "The Calvin Cycle produces glucose",
    "answer": true
  },

  {
    "question": "Reduction is losing elections",
    "answer": false
  },

  {
    "question": "Ellen's favorite animal is a bluebird",
    "answer": false
  },

  {
    "question": "The Krebs Cycle is aerobic.",
    "answer": true
  },

  {
    "question": "The Krebs Cycle produced many oxidized electron carriers",
    "answer": false
  },

  {
    "question": "The knot in pretzels represent hands clasped in prayer",
    "answer": true
  }
]